The biggest thing is that the figure I
mentioned
is the maximum of the youth
generation and their deaths, their
families and
friends are not restricted there. In
our country, the economy of our state is also being
damaged. The
state is where the
students are studying, be it in government
institutes
or others. Every state has
an expenditure involvement.
We have been created to
serve in any field,
any area. Some may be teachers,
some doctors, some will go to
other departments, some will go to administration. So
when I or someone who is taking my life prematurely, when it is
time for the country to give something to the society, he is gone. It is very
painful. We want
that together we all should bring this road, which is a traffic
accident, under control in any way
and the only way is to
follow the traffic rules and route safety rules. A
simple
concept of law is that if you
look at the law, the law will not look at you. If you do
not look at the law, the law will look at you.
Seeing the importance of the national level,  Just
recently we have
observed Route Safety Month from 15th
January to 14th
February. We used to observe Route Safety Week
but
considering the
seriousness on road
safety at the national level, that Road Safety Week has
now become Road Safety Month.
It is easy to understand that
its importance is increasing at the national level as well.
Road
safety is being given importance.
[Music]
الله الله